

CONTACT

- 01136693307
- uarehup@gmail.com
- Johor, Malaysia, 41, Jalan Redang 2/6, Taman Redang, 81100 Johor Bahru, Johor.

EXPERTISE

Skills in Java Programming

Skills in C++ programming

React Web Development

Android App Development (Android Studio)

LANGUAGES

Chinese Proficient

English Intermediate

Malay Intermediate

SKILLS

C++

Java

Python

React

NG WEI JIAN

BIOGRAPHY

Aloha!

My name is Ng Wei Jian, born in 1st January 1999, Johor Bahru, Malaysia. I am a second-year Computer Science student from Faculty of Computing Informatics, Multimedia University Cyberjaya, and my specialization is Software Engineering with current CGPA **3.09**.

For my hobbies, I like to have some physical workouts (like badminton, marathon) to keep my mind disciplined so I still can stay active on my academics. Other than physical workout, I like to solve some common algorithm questions on **LeetCode** platform, and it really help me to refresh my problem solving skills!

ABOUT ME



Academic Level Bachelor Degree



Gender Male



Age 23



MMU Student ID

EDUCATION

2021 - Present

Bachelor in Computer Science (Specialization: Software Engineering) Multimedia University Cyberjaya Current CGPA 3.09

2018 - 2021

Diploma In Information Technology (IT) Multimedia University Malacca CGPA 3.5

2012 - 2017

SPM certificate SMK Taman Molek Grade with 4A & 3B

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - 2019

Quality Management System (QMS) Internship at Maruwa (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd, located at Batu Berendam, Malacca, Malaysia

Develop a simple data entry program to ease the workload of data entry and minimize errors from manual data entry (Main Project in IT internship):- Using Visual Basic programming Create & Update Procedure Manual for production workflow:- Deal with procedure standardization for every production department with proper documentation skills to emphasize on the quality control of products such as magnet for magnetic products, substrate for ceramic products. Daily Inspection Quality Control:- Inspect quality on the production spot and perform data entries into Microsoft Excel and save it for quality maintenance purpose. Communication skills using English (80%) & Malay (20%):- Daily meeting with manager and other colleagues. Mainly report for task progress and some feedbacks on quality control.

2018 - 2018

Clerk in Transportation Company BananaLimo Transportation Sdn. Bhd Basic communication formal written & verbal skills in English & Japanese:- Deal with



mainly Japanese customer\'s queries regarding transportation per request via email and WhatsApp. Basic Excel data entry skills:- Key in average 50+ daily sales into Excel. Basic Excel data sum up and chart skills:- Sum up daily sales into weekly and convert it into line chart with Excel to analyze the sales performance.